Teja Manne

Software Engineer (Full Stack Web Application Developer)

Email tejazz.manne@gmail.com Phone +91 8939-715-245

Linkedin linkedin.com/in/tejamanne Address 1/21, Mamidalapadu, Kurnool - 518004, AP

A highly dynamic and diligent Software Engineer offering nearly 7 years of experience with a demonstrated history of working in the healthcare, financial service and market research industries. Expert in problem solving, building project framework and architecture, candidate recruitment, training and management.

I want to work with a professionally managed organisation in a challenging environment which gives me an opportunity to enhance my learning, sharpen my skills and add value through my work.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Nielsen, Chennai — Software Engineer

May 2019 - PRESENT

Fidelity Investments, Chennai — Software Engineer

Aug 2017 - May 2019

L - Cube Innovative Solutions, Chennai — Software Engineer

July 2014 - July 2017

ROLES AND RESPONSIBILITIES

- Full stack web application development (design, development, deployment).
- Building project framework and architectures.
- Problem solving at the workplace.
- L3 support for versatile applications.
- Handling the interviews and internship programmes.

EDUCATION

Jawaharlal Nehru Technological University Anantapur, Anantapur

— B. Tech (Computer Science) - 74.5%

SKILLS

Languages

Java

Javascript (ES6)

HTML/CSS

SQL/NoSQL

Databases

MySQL

Postgres

Mongodb

Web Technologies

Spring Boot

Spring Data JPA

Spring Security

Restful Web Services

React is

React Redux

React Material UI

AWS (Basics)

PROJECTS

Shopper Explorer — Market Research application — **Nielsen**

Consumer goods panel reporting application which helps the clients to analyze the sales of their products in various perspectives.

Accounting Expense System — Expense application — Fidelity Investments

Accounting Expense System(AES) calculates the expenses for the funds.

FPCMS FUN OPS — Fun Ops application — Fidelity Investments

System integration analysis and design application

AppFlow — System Integration Analysis and Design application — **Fidelity Investments**

System integration analysis and design application

Patient Portal — Healthcare application — L-Cube Innovative Solutions

Patient Portal is a secure online web application that gives patients convenient 24/7 access to personal health information.

Glace Kiosk — Healthcare Kiosk application — L-Cube Innovative Solutions

Glace interactive kiosk provides access to patients to register, update information in the chart, create an encounter, fill the intake forms/consent forms and also pay bills.

Glace Analytics — Analytics application — L-Cube Innovative Solutions

Glace Analytics is an application to get insights into our company's various applications operations and improve the performance of business operations. Administration dashboards for Server, reminders, billing, labs e.t.c and reports are the parts of our analytics application.

Declaration

T 1	1	1	1 .		1 .1	1 , 1	c · 1	1 1	1		1 .	~ 11		•	1 1	1
	10roh	XI da	alara 1	that al	I tha	dataile.	turnich	വര	bove are 1	trua to 1	ha 1	7111	act at	mi	Iznowi.	$\Delta d \alpha \Delta$
	ICICI	vuu	CIAICI	mai ai	1 1110 0	JULATIS	10111151	ועט מ	DOVE ALC			1111	COL OI	1111	KIIU)WI	CUEU

Date:	Signature:
Place:	(Teja Manne)